Katie Ebbing

UX UI Designer

New York City, NY

Phone- 217-257-2515

Email- kateebbing@gmail.com

Portfolio- kateebbing.com (coming soon!)

Linkedin- linkedin.com/in/katie-ebbing-a1491112/

Behance- behance.net/katieebbing

Skills

Figma
Sketch
Adobe XD
Adobe Suite
Miro
Heuristic Evaluations
Usability Testing
Design Thinker
Problem Solver

UX/UI designer based in New York City with a passion for designing accessible and inclusive websites and apps. Earning a certificate of UX/UI at Columbia University, Google UX Design Professional Certificate through Coursera and Graduated Magna Cum Laude with a Bachelor of Science for Art Management with a specialization in Graphic Design at Quincy University.

Education

Columbia University/ UX UI Certificate

November 2020 - June 2021, New York City, NY

Google Professional Certificate through Coursera/ UX Design

February 2021 - June 2021, New York City, NY

Quincy University / Art Management

September 2006 - May 2010, Quincy, Illinois

Graduated Magna Cum Laude, Captain on Division II Volleyball Team, Winner of Mary S. Oakley Award at the Quincy Art Center for a water-color self portrait.

Experience

House Manager/Personal Assistant / Private Home

September 2018 - PRESENT, New York City

House Manager and Personal Assistant for a private residence in the Upper West Side. Overseeing and managing renovations. Meeting every need of the employer in a timely and efficient manner.

Property and Hospitality Manager / Bahamas

September 2015 - July 2017, Bahamas

Chief Stewardess / Private Yachts

June 2010 - September 2015, Mederteranian Sea